{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
            "correct_answer": "Object Oriented",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Object Based",
                "Procedural",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
            "correct_answer": "Both A and B",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "var",
                "let",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
            "correct_answer": "Both A and B",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "getElementbyId()",
                "getElementsByClassName()",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
            "correct_answer": "const",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "var",
                "let",
                "constant"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
            "correct_answer": "All of the above",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "document.write()",
                "console.log()",
                "window.alert()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "JavaScript",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
            "correct_answer": "in",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "is in",
                "exists",
                "lies"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "CSS",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": " CSS stands for -",
            "correct_answer": "Cascading style sheets",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Color and style sheets",
                "Cascade style sheets",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "CSS",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
            "correct_answer": "background-color",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "bgcolor",
                "color",
                "All of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "CSS",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
            "correct_answer": "font-size",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "text-style",
                "text-size",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "CSS",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is -",
            "correct_answer": "style",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "styles",
                "class",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "CSS",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The HTML attribute used to define the internal stylesheet is -",
            "correct_answer": "<style>",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "style",
                "<link>",
                "<script>"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
